<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Formula 1 Regulations</string>
    <string name="tech">Technical</string>
    <string name="sport">Sporting</string>
    <string name="fin">Financial</string>
    <string name="actualYear" translatable="false">2020</string>
    <string name="nextYear" translatable="false">2021</string>
    <string name="farFuture" translatable="false">2022</string>
    <string name="techTitle">Formula 1 Technical Regulations</string>
    <string name="sportTitle">Formula 1 Sporting Regulations</string>
    <string name="finTitle">Formula 1 Financial Regulations</string>
	<string-array name="tech_20">
		<item>DEFINITIONS
			<!--1.1-->%s Formula One Car
				%c An automobile designed solely for speed races on circuits or closed courses.
			<!--1.2-->%s Automobile
				%c A land vehicle running on at least four non-aligned complete wheels, of which at least two are used for steering and at least two for propulsion.
			<!--1.3-->%s Land Vehicle
				%c A locomotive device propelled by its own means, moving by constantly taking real support on the earth\'s surface, of which the propulsion and steering are under the control of a driver aboard the vehicle.
			<!--1.4-->%s Bodywork
				%c All entirely sprung parts of the car in contact with the external air stream, except cameras, camera housings, rear view mirrors as defined in Article 14.3, ERS status lights, the secondary roll structure and associated fixings and fairings and the parts definitely associated with the mechanical functioning of the engine, transmission and running gear. Airboxes, radiators and engine exhausts are considered to be part of the bodywork.
					%r14.3,tech20,14,3
			<!--1.5-->%s Wheel
				%c Flange and rim.
			<!--1.6-->%s Complete wheel
				%c Wheel and inflated tyre. The complete wheel is considered part of the suspension system.
			<!--1.7-->%s Automobile Make
				%c In the case of Formula racing cars, an automobile make is a complete car. When the car manufacturer fits an engine which it does not manufacture, the car shall be considered a hybrid and the name of the engine manufacturer shall be associated with that of the car manufacturer. The name of the car manufacturer must always precede that of the engine manufacturer. Should a hybrid car win a Championship Title, Cup or Trophy, this will be awarded to the manufacturer of the car.
			<!--1.8-->%s Event
				%c Any event entered into the FIA F1 Championship Calendar for any year commencing 24 hours before P1 is scheduled to take place and including all practice and the race itself and ending at the later of the time for the lodging of a protest under the terms of the Sporting Code and the time when a technical or sporting verification has been carried out under the terms of that Code, whichever is the later.
			<!--1.9-->%s Weight
				%c Is the weight of the car with the driver, wearing his complete racing apparel, at all times during the Event.
			<!--1.10-->%s Engine cubic capacity
				%c The volume swept in the cylinders of the engine by the movement of the pistons. This volume shall be expressed in cubic centimetres. In calculating engine cubic capacity, the number Pi shall be 3.1416.
			<!--1.11-->%s Pressure charging
				%c Increasing the weight of the charge of the fuel/air mixture in the combustion chamber (over the weight induced by normal atmospheric pressure, ram effect and dynamic effects in the intake and/or exhaust system) by any means whatsoever. The injection of fuel under pressure is not considered to be pressure charging.
			<!--1.12-->%s Cockpit
				%c The volume which accommodates the driver.
			<!--1.13-->%s Sprung suspension
				%c The means whereby all complete wheels are suspended from the unit comprising the survival cell\/power unit\/gearbox by a spring medium.
			<!--1.14-->%s Survival cell
				%c The continuous closed structure containing the fuel tank, the cockpit and the parts of the ES listed in Article 5.12.7.
					%r5.12,tech20,5,12
			<!--1.15-->%s Camera
				%c Television cameras the dimensions of which are defined in Drawing 6.
					%rDrawing 6,tech20,24,6
			<!--1.16-->%s Camera housing
				%c A device which is identical in shape and weight to a camera and which is supplied by the relevant competitor for fitting to his car in lieu of a camera.
			<!--1.17-->%s Cockpit padding
				%c Non-structural parts placed within the cockpit for the sole purpose of improving driver comfort and safety. All such material must be quickly removable without the use of tools.
			<!--1.18-->%s Brake caliper
				%c All parts of the braking system outside the survival cell, other than brake discs, brake pads, caliper pistons, components directly associated with the system referred to in Article 11.9, brake hoses and fittings, which are stressed when subjected to the braking pressure. Bolts or studs which are used for attachment are not considered to be part of the braking system.
					%r11.9,tech20,11,9
			<!--1.19-->%s Electronically controlled
				%c Any command system or process that utilises semi-conductor or thermionic technology.
			<!--1.20-->%s Open and closed sections
				%c A section will be considered closed if it is fully complete within the dimensioned boundary to which it is referenced, if it is not it will be considered open.
			<!--1.21-->%s Power train
				%c The power unit and associated torque transmission systems, up to but not including the drive shafts.
			<!--1.22-->%s Power unit
				%c The internal combustion engine, complete with its ancillaries, any energy recovery system and all actuation systems necessary to make them function at all times.
			<!--1.23-->%s Engine
				%c The internal combustion engine including ancillaries and actuator systems necessary for its proper function.
			<!--1.24-->%s Energy Recovery System (ERS)
				%c A system that is designed to recover energy from the car, store that energy and make it available to propel the car and, optionally, to drive any ancillaries and actuation systems necessary for its proper function.
			<!--1.25-->%s Motor Generator Unit - Kinetic (MGU-K)
				%c The Kinetic Motor Generator Unit is the electrical machine mechanically linked to the drive train as part of the ERS.
			<!--1.26-->%s Motor Generator Unit - Heat (MGU-H)
				%c The Heat Motor Generator Unit is the electrical machine linked to the exhaust turbine of a pressure charging system as part of the ERS.
			<!--1.27-->%s Energy Store (ES)
				%c The part of ERS that stores energy, including its safety control electronics and a minimal housing.
			<!--1.28-->%s Compressor inlet
				%c A component containing a duct of closed cross section through which all air destined for combustion enters any compressor; the duct must extend upstream of any part of any variable geometry device permitted by Article 5.9.
					%r5.9,tech20,5,9
			<!--1.29-->%s Compressor outlet
				%c A component containing a duct of closed cross section through which all air destined for combustion exits a compressor.
			<!--1.30-->%s Combustion chamber
				%c An enclosed space in the engine cylinder controlled by the opening and closing of the poppet valves in which combustion takes place.
			<!--1.31-->%s Fuel injector
				%c Any device or component that delivers fuel into an oxidiser.
			<!--1.32-->%s Auxiliary Oil Tank (AOT)
				%c An Auxiliary Oil Tank (AOT) is a singular vessel connected to the engine whose sole function is to hold engine oil for the replenishment of the engine lubrication system.
			<!--1.33-->%s Engine exhaust system
				%c Assembly of parts conveying the engine exhaust gases from the engine exhaust flange up to but not including the turbine and\/or wastegate. It does not include the turbine or wastegate exit tail-pipe(s). A set comprises left and right assemblies.
			<!--1.34-->%s Power Unit Control Electronics (PU-CE)
				%c Any component used to control Power Unit sub-systems and containing programmable semiconductors or high power switching devices.
				%p It includes, but is not limited to, MGU-K control unit, MGU-H control unit, injector control unit, ignition control unit, DC-DC.
				%p It excludes any FIA Standard ECU, FIA sensors and ES safety control electronics.
		</item>
		<item>GENERAL PRINCIPLES
			<!--2.1-->%s Role of the FIA
				%c The following technical regulations for Formula One cars are issued by the FIA.
			<!--2.2-->%s Amendments to the regulations
				%c These Technical Regulations apply to the Championship taking place in the calendar year referred to in the title (“the Championship”) and may only be changed after 30 April of the preceding year with the unanimous agreement of all competitors, save for changes made by the FIA for safety reasons which may come into effect without notice or delay.
			<!--2.3-->%s Dangerous construction
				%c The stewards may exclude a vehicle whole construction is deemed to be dangerous.
			<!--2.4-->%s Compliance with the regulations
				%c Automobiles must comply with these regulations in their entirety at all times during an Event.
				%p Should a competitor introduce a new design or system or feel that any aspect of these regulations is unclear, clarification may be sought from the FIA Formula One Technical Department. If clarification relates to any new design or system, correspondence must include:
					%a &lt;b&gt;a.&lt;\/b&gt; A full description of the design or system.
					%a &lt;b&gt;b.&lt;\/b&gt; Drawings or schematics where appropriate.
					%a &lt;b&gt;c.&lt;\/b&gt; The competitor\'s opinion concerning the immediate implications on other parts of the car of any proposed new design.
					%a &lt;b&gt;d.&lt;\/b&gt; The competitor\'s opinion concerning any possible long term consequences or new developments which may come from using any such new designs or systems.
					%a &lt;b&gt;e.&lt;\/b&gt; The precise way or ways in which the competitor feels the new design or system will enhance the performance of the car.
			<!--2.5-->%s New systems or technologies
				%c Any new system, procedure or technology not specifically covered by these regulations, but which is deemed permissible by the FIA Formula One Technical Department, will only be admitted until the end of the Championship during which it is introduced. Following this the Formula One Commission will be asked to review the technology concerned and, if they feel it adds no value to Formula One in general, it will be specifically prohibited.
				%p Any team whose technology is prohibited in this way will then be required to publish full technical details of the relevant system or procedure.
			<!--2.6-->%s Measurements
				%c All measurements must be made while the car is stationary on a flat horizontal surface.
			<!--2.7-->%s Duty of Competitor
				%c It is the duty of each competitor to satisfy the FIA technical delegate and the stewards that his automobile complies with these regulations in their entirety at all times during an Event.
				%p The design of the car, its components and systems shall, with the exception of safety features, demonstrate their compliance with these regulations by means of physical inspection of hardware or materials. No mechanical design may rely upon software inspection as a means of ensuring its compliance.
				%p Due to their nature, the compliance of electronic systems may be assessed by means of inspection of hardware, software and data.
		</item>
	</string-array>
    <string name="techTitle20">2020 Formula 1 Technical Regulations</string>
	<string name="references">References</string>
</resources>