<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Formula 1 Regulations</string>
    <string name="tech">Technical</string>
    <string name="sport">Sporting</string>
    <string name="fin">Financial</string>
    <string name="actualYear" translatable="false">2020</string>
    <string name="nextYear" translatable="false">2021</string>
    <string name="farFuture" translatable="false">2022</string>
    <string name="techTitle">Formula 1 Technical Regulations</string>
    <string name="sportTitle">Formula 1 Sporting Regulations</string>
    <string name="finTitle">Formula 1 Financial Regulations</string>
    <string-array name="tech_20">
        <item>DEFINITIONS %s Formula One Car %c An automobile designed solely for speed races on circuits or closed courses. $s Automobile %c A land vehicle running on at least four non-aligned complete wheels, of which at least two are used for steering and at least two for propulsion. %s Land Vehicle %c A locomotive device propelled by its own means, moving by constantly taking real support on the earth\'s surface, of which the propulsion and steering are under the control of a driver aboard the vehicle. %s Bodywork %c All entirely sprung parts of the car in contact with the external air stream, except cameras, camera housings, rear view mirrors as defined in Article 14.3, ERS status lights, the secondary roll structure and associated fixings and fairings and the parts definitely associated with the mechanical functioning of the engine, transmission and running gear. Airboxes, radiators and engine exhausts are considered to be part of the bodywork. %s Wheel %c Flange and rim. %s Complete wheel %c Wheel and inflated tyre. The complete wheel is considered part of the suspension system. %s Automobile Make %c In the case of Formula racing cars, an automobile make is a complete car. When the car manufacturer fits an engine which it does not manufacture, the car shall be considered a hybrid and the name of the engine manufacturer shall be associated with that of the car manufacturer. The name of the car manufacturer must always precede that of the engine manufacturer. Should a hybrid car win a Championship Title, Cup or Trophy, this will be awarded to the manufacturer of the car. %s Event %c Any event entered into the FIA F1 Championship Calendar for any year commencing 24 hours before P1 is scheduled to take place and including all practice and the race itself and ending at the later of the time for the lodging of a protest under the terms of the Sporting Code and the time when a technical or sporting verification has been carried out under the terms of that Code, whichever is the later. %s Weight %c Is the weight of the car with the driver, wearing his complete racing apparel, at all times during the Event. %s Engine cubic capacity %c The volume swept in the cylinders of the engine by the movement of the pistons. This volume shall be expressed in cubic centimetres. In calculating engine cubic capacity, the number Pi shall be 3.1416. %s Pressure charging %c Increasing the weight of the charge of the fuel/air mixture in the combustion chamber (over the weight induced by normal atmospheric pressure, ram effect and dynamic effects in the intake and/or exhaust system) by any means whatsoever. The injection of fuel under pressure is not considered to be pressure charging. %s Cockpit %c The volume which accommodates the driver. %s Sprung suspension %c The means whereby all complete wheels are suspended from the unit comprising the survival cell\/power unit\/gearbox by a spring medium. %s Survival cell %c The continuous closed structure containing the fuel tank, the cockpit and the parts of the ES listed in Article 5.12.7. %s Camera %c Television cameras the dimensions of which are defined in Drawing 6. %s Camera housing %c A device which is identical in shape and weight to a camera and which is supplied by the relevant competitor for fitting to his car in lieu of a camera. %s Cockpit padding %c Non-structural parts placed within the cockpit for the sole purpose of improving driver comfort and safety. All such material must be quickly removable without the use of tools. %s Brake caliper %c All parts of the braking system outside the survival cell, other than brake discs, brake pads, caliper pistons, components directly associated with the system referred to in Article 11.9, brake hoses and fittings, which are stressed when subjected to the braking pressure. Bolts or studs which are used for attachment are not considered to be part of the braking system.</item> <!--1.18-->
        <item>GENERAL PRINCIPLES %s Role of the FIA %c The following technical regulations for Formula One cars are issued by the FIA. %s Amendments to the regulations %c These Technical Regulations apply to the Championship taking place in the calendar year referred to in the title (“the Championship”) and may only be changed after 30 April of the preceding year with the unanimous agreement of all competitors, save for changes made by the FIA for safety reasons which may come into effect without notice or delay.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="techTitle20">2020 Formula 1 Technical Regulations</string>
</resources>